let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is the best way to authenticate yourself?",
        answer: "D. All of the Above",
        options: [
            "A. Passwords",
            "B. passphrases",
            "C. Biometrics",
            "D. All of the Above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What does Cyber resileince mean",
        answer: "A. The ability to protect electronic data and systems from cyberattacks",
        options: [
            "A. The ability to protect electronic data and systems from cyberattacks",
            "B. Blocking spam and phishing emails",
            "C. The ability to navigate in the internet safely",
            "D. Not getting addicted to social media"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What can happen to a bank that gets hacked?",
        answer: "D. All of the above",
        options: [
            "A. Financial losses",
            "B. Service outages",
            "C. Reputational damage",
            "D. All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What type of software infects a machine, locks the files, then asks for money?",
        answer: "C. Ransomware",
        options: [
            "A. Worm",
            "B. Trojan",
            "C. Ransomware",
            "D. Browser Hijacker"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is a group of computers networked together and used by hackers to steal information called?",
        answer: "A. Rootkit",
        options: [
            "A. Rootkit",
            "B. Operating System",
            "C. Botnet",
            "D. DDoS"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What does the term 'firewall' refer to in cyber security?",
        answer: "C. A security system that monitors and controls network traffic",
        options: [
            "A. A protective suit worn by cybersecurity professionals",
            "B. A physical barrier around computer servers",
            "C. A security system that monitors and controls network traffic",
            "D. Software for preventing computer overheating"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which one of the following could lead to the spread of a malicious program?",
        answer: "C. Using a USB Flash Drive from an unknown source to exchange data",
        options: [
            "A. Using only software that has been checked for viruses",
            "B. Maintaining regularly uptated anti-virus software",
            "C. Using a USB Flash Drive from an unknown source to exchange data",
            "D. Opening only virus-checked file attachments from known sources"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What is the primary purpose of a VPN (Virtual Private Network) in cyber security?",
        answer: "B. Encrypt and secure communication over the internet",
        options: [
            "A. Speed up internet connection",
            "B. Encrypt and secure communication over the internet",
            "C. Block malicious websites",
            "D. Boost Wi-Fi signal strength"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which one of the following describes spam?",
        answer: "D. Sending unwanted bulk messages",
        options: [
            "A. Gathering information about a person or organisation without their knowledge",
            "B. Performing an unathorised, usually malicious, action such as erasing files",
            "C. Putting unnecessary load on the network by making copies of files",
            "D. Sending unwanted bulk messages"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which one of the following can protect a computer from the risk of unwanted emails?",
        answer: "A. Anti-spam software",
        options: [
            "A. Anti-spam software",
            "B. Anti-virus software",
            "C. Anti-spyware software",
            "D. PC diagnostic software"
        ]
    }
];